OLAKUNLE SALAMI

3963 Neyland Valley Dr. Memphis, TN, 38135 | (901) 603-0428 | Kennylanre9@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I would like to put my experience of troubleshooting and repairing hardware to better use. I have been working with electronics since I was 10. I took apart my first electronics (a PlayStation 3 controller) and successfully repaired it. I'm very tenacious towards finishing projects which I started. I have strong leadership skills and proven track records. I am looking forward to working with a company where we both benefit from each other's experience.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Created my own website portfolio: https://olakunles.github.io/portfolio/index.html
- Computer skills include: Advanced user of Microsoft words, Excel, Power Point, developed spreadsheet using excel; 50 wpm, also performed extensive word processing.

EXPERIENCE

08/2016-05/2018

Member, Future Business Leaders of America (FBLA)

- Obtained the required clusters in General Business Training and IT training with other members.
- Earned 6th place of the Web Design cluster in the national conference.

08/2016-05/2018

Two Year experience with code programming languages such python, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

- Took three courses in computer programming where first course was web design learning basic HTML and CSs.
- Took coding 1 which assisted me to further my skills in HTML and CSS. I also learned python.
- Took AP computer science which focused more on Java and binary code.

08/2015-05/2016

A year experience with the CISCO Networking Academy learning in ITE essentials including PC Hardware with certification and cover letter.

- Took Introduction to information technology.
- Studied the introduction to the internet and information technology essentials with 12 different chapters including PC hardware.
- Disassembled and reassembled a desktop into working condition.
- Completed the course with a certification and cover letter.

EDUCATION

08/2014-05/2014

High School Diploma, Memphis TN, Bartlett High 3.5GPA

- Honor Roll Student with a 3.5 GPA.
- ACT Score of 24 with a 30+ in science.

08/2017-Present

Memphis TN, University of Memphis

COMMUNICATION

- Good presentation skills with experience showcasing my websites.
- Good verbal skills in formal gatherings.
- Experienced in formal communication with my elders and peers.

LEADERSHIP

- Earned seniority and presidency of my school's FBLA (Future Business Leader of America) club.
- Communicated with my adviser and club members about assisting with and participated in the fundraising.
- Assisted peers with getting into the National Leadership Conference.
- Demonstrated good qualities in the 2018 National Leadership Conference and awarded certifications.

References:

Available upon request.